{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "RRRReact Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application."
    },
    {
      "name": "API calls",
      "description": "learn to make API calls and CRUD functionality",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "testinggg",
      "description": "test",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "dfgfgsd",
      "description": "fdfzff",
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "aaaaaaaaaaWhat path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "aaaaaaaaAll paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "CRUD",
      "back": "create, read, update, delete",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "name": "",
      "description": "",
      "front": "dfd",
      "back": "fdsfdsad",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "name": "",
      "description": "",
      "front": "hi",
      "back": "heeello",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "name": "",
      "description": "",
      "front": "hi",
      "back": "heeello",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "name": "",
      "description": "",
      "front": "hi",
      "back": "heeello",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "csard",
      "back": "carddd",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "xccx",
      "back": "cxzc",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "m   m",
      "back": "m mm ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "weradsgzt",
      "back": "fsdgffx",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "front": "fdsfz",
      "back": "fdfz",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "efwtd",
      "back": "edrdf",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "qqqqqqq",
      "back": "qqqqqqqqqqq",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "ddddddddd",
      "back": "ddddddddddd",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "hihii",
      "back": "yoyoy",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "card": [],
      "front": "a card",
      "back": "is bored",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 22
    }
  ]
}